All right. So this is where things start to get
现在，我们将设置一些有趣的界面了
fun if you have not been having fun already.
到目前为止还都没介绍什么有趣的内容
So what we are going to do now is build out this view.
我们将构建这个视图
You will notice here that what we are doing is this is kind of like a live detailed view.
相当于一个实时详情视图
What we are doing is we are pulling information
我们将从手机中获取信息
from the phone in order to render this view.
并渲染该视图
So it shows which way we are heading,
它会显示我们正朝着哪个方向前进
the altitude, the current speed.
海拔是多少，当前移动速度是多少
All of this is going to be coming from your phone.
所有这些信息都来自于手机
So in order to do that, we actually need to go ahead and
因此，我们需要
use the phone's API to get that information.
使用手机的 API 来获得这些信息
And one side note, if you are trying to do this on Android in the
顺便提醒下，如果你尝试在 Android 模拟器上跟着操作
simulator,is probably not going to work for some reason.
可能会因为某些原因而出现故障
The Android simulator does not work with what we are doing,
Android 模拟器不能实现我们要执行的操作
but if you have it on a actual real device using the Expo app, you will be fine.
但是如果你在实际设备上使用 Expo 应用，则一切正常
So you either forget about the Android emulator and use the Expo app
因此请别使用 Android 模拟器，而是使用 Expo 应用
or the iOS simulator. All right. Let us jump into it.
或 iOS 模拟器。我们开始吧
So what we are going to do is,
转到此处
this new view is going to be called Live.js.
新建一个视图文件，叫做 Live.js
What we are going to have for now is
暂时先导入
just react in a component and then we will import the View,
react，
Text and this thing called ActivityIndicator,
然后导入 View、Text 以及 ActivityIndicator
which are all coming from react-native.
都来自于 react-native
And then we will go ahead and export this class which extends component.
然后导出这个扩展自 component 的类
So what state this component is going to have,
设定此组件的状态
it is going to have some coordinates which are set to null initially.
包括坐标，暂时设为 null
It is going to have a status which we will also set to
还包括 status，也设为 null
null and a direction which is just going to be an empty string.
以及 direction，设为空字符串
So what we can do is we can grab this information off of the state.
我们可以从 this.state 上获取这些信息
And then there are a few different views that we are going to get
我们将获取几个不同的视图
depending on the specific permissions that you are granted.
具体取决于你所获得的权限
So what we are going to say is if status equals null,
如果 status === null
so the user really has not given us any permissions yet,
表示用户尚未授予任何权限
nothing has changed from the default state,
依然保持默认状态
then what we want to do is render an ActivityIndicator,
则渲染 ActivityIndicator
and we will give it a margin top of 30.
并将 marginTop 设为 30
All in ActivityIndicator is it's basically a loading spinners.
ActivityIndicator 中的内容只是表示正在加载的旋转图标
So you've seen it before. It's just going render a spinner like,
你之前见过，它只是在渲染旋转图标
"Hey, we are waiting on something."
仿佛在提示系统正在等待中
If the status equals denied,
如果 status === denied
meaning you asked for permission and they did not give it to you,
表示你请求了权限，但是遭到用户拒绝
what we are going to do for now is just render a view with some text in that says denied,
我们暂时渲染一个视图，在其中显示文本“Denied”
and then we are going to do this exact same thing,
然后我们将执行完全一样的操作
but instead of denied,
但是这里的 denied
it is going to be for undetermined.
将改为 undetermined
And when you are messing around with the simulator, again,
当你在模拟器中操作时
some of these permissions are going to be a little bit
某些权限会比较卡顿
wonky because we are not on an actual real device,
因为我们没有在实际设备上操作
but we will get to that when we get to that.
但是可以实现最终目标
And then lastly, if it is not denied or undetermined,
最后，如果不是 denied 或 undetermined
that means it was granted.
则表明授予了权限
So what we will say is,
我们将
we will render a view,
渲染一个视图
and then for now,
暂时
what we are going to do is we will render a few text components.
我们将渲染几个文本组件
We will just go ahead and show the state for now,
暂时显示这个状态
and this looks pretty good.
看起来不错
So let us go ahead and add this as a new tab.
我们将这个当做新的标签页添加进来
So inside of App.js,
转到 App.js
first, we need to import it.
首先需要导入该组件
And next, what we need to do is inside of tabs,
接着，转到 Tabs 中
let us go ahead and add any property.
添加一个新的属性
We will call it Live,
称之为 Live
and just as we have done before,
就像之前一样
screen is going to be the Live component.
screen 设为 Live 组件
Some options here, the tabBarLabe,
添加一些导航选项
we're just going to just say Live,
将 tabBarLabel 设为 Live
and then I am actually just going to copy
然后复制这段代码
this one because we are also going to use Ionicon font,
因为我们将使用 Ionicon 字体
but the name of this one is going to be ios-speedometer.
但是将 name 改为 ios-speedometer
All right, let us see if this is working.
看看是否可行
So we got a Live.
转到 Live
Notice, we get an indicator.
注意，这里出现了旋转指示符
That is because the current status is set to null,
因为当前 status 设为 null
so we can just assume that this is working for sure.
我们假设可行
We can set it to denied.
当然可以设为 denied
Now, what we should see it is denied up here.
现在应该能在这里看到 denied
All right. Let's set this back to null,
重新设为 null
and we will continue building this out in future videos.
我们将在后续视频中继续完善这一部分